brilliantdirectories.com 2017-03-21

# Our Privacy Policy - Directory Software - Directory Script - Directory Template

## We Value Security & Privacy

Brilliant Directories respects the privacy of our users and has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe for you, as an individual who is a user of Brilliant Directories (and all websites and URL's controlled or operated by Brilliant Directories which link to this policy, unless otherwise specified) or our services, or otherwise provide us with information through various means the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures.

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or services or transacting business with us. By using our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us.

**_Information we collect about you_**

_In General_. We may collect personal information that can identify you such as your name and email address and other information that does not identify you. When you provide personal information through our website, the information may be sent to servers located in the United States and other countries around the world.

  * **Information you provide.** We may collect and store any personal information you enter on our website or provide to us in some other manner. This includes identifying information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number, and in addition, for Professionals, your credit card number and other personally identifiable information. We also may request information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information
  * **Information from other sources.** We may also periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from other business partners, contractors and other third parties. Examples of information that we may receive include (but are not limited to): updated delivery and address information, purchase history, and additional demographic information.
  * **Information about others.** We may also collect and store personal information about other people that you provide to us. If you use our website to send others (friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.) information that may interest them through our system, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of each such recipient

_Use of cookies and other technologies to collect information._ We use various technologies to collect information from your computer and about your activities on our site.

  * **Information collected automatically.** We automatically collect information from your browser when you visit our website. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us (see "Cookies" below), and the referring website address.
  * **Cookies.** When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our website.
  * **Other Technologies.** We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our site. We also may include web beacons in promotional [or other] e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our website visitors to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities.

**_How we use the information we collect_**

_In general._ We may use information that we collect about you to:

  * deliver the products and services that you have requested;
  * manage your account and provide you with customer support;
  * perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others;
  * communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices or send newsletters about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or other third parties;
  * communicate with you with regard to partially completed service requests;
  * develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site and other sites;
  * verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes;
  * perform background screening, which may include the use of third parties, on Service Professionals
  * enforce our terms and conditions;
  * manage our business and
  * perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

_Financial information._ For our users, we may use financial information or payment method to process payment for any purchases made on our website, enroll you in the discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate, to pre-qualify you for credit card and other offers that you might find of interest, to pre-qualify users to participate in our directory service, to protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.

_Job applicants._ If your personal information is submitted through our website when applying for a position with our company, the information will be used solely in connection with considering and acting upon your application. We may retain your personal information for a period of time, but only for the purpose of considering your application for current or future available positions. This information may be shared with our other companies for the purpose of evaluating your qualifications for the particular position or other available positions, as well as with third-party service providers retained by us to collect, maintain and analyze candidate submissions for job postings.

**_With whom we share your information_**

We want you to understand when and with whom we may share personal or other information we have collected about you or your activities on our web site or while using our services.

_Personal information._ We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated below or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal information shared. We may share personal information with:

  * **Authorized service providers:** We may share your personal information with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, processing credit card payments, delivering packages, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our website or performing background checks of Professionals. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.
  * **Business partners:** When you make purchases, reservations or engage in promotions offered through our website or our services, we may share personal information with the businesses with which we partner to offer you those products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant's offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant.
  * **Other Situations.** We also may disclose your information:
  * In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
  * When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our website terms and conditions or other agreements or policies.
  * In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Any third parties to whom we may disclose personal information may have their own privacy policies which describe how they use and disclose personal information. Those policies will govern use, handling and disclosure of your personal information once we have shared it with those third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. If you want to learn more about their privacy practices, we encourage you to visit the websites of those third parties. These entities or their servers may be located either inside or outside the United States.

**_Third-party websites_**

There are a number of places on our website where you may click on a link to access other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement or a search result on our website, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites you visit by clicking on the "privacy" link typically located at the bottom of the webpage you are visiting.

**_How you can access your information_**

If you have an online account with us, you have the ability to review and update your personal information online by logging into your account. You can also review and update your personal information by contacting us. More information about how to contact us is provided below.

You can also choose to have your account disabled by contacting service@BrilliantDirectories.com. After you deactivate your account, you will not be able to sign in to our website or access any of your personal information. However, you can open a new account at any time. If you deactivate your account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, enforce our terms and conditions, take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of our web site or our users, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties' policies.

**_Your choices about collection and use of your information_**

  * You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our service because such information may be required in order for you to register as a member of our directory service; to use our services; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on our website.
  * At any time a consumer user can choose to no longer receive commercial or promotional emails or newsletters from us by accessing your user account and opting out. You also will be given the opportunity, in any commercial e-mail that we send to you, to opt out of receiving such messages in the future. It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request. We may send you other types of transactional and relationship e-mail communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.
  * If you prefer not to have us share your postal mailing information with these selected providers of goods and services that may be of interest to you, you can notify us at any time by emailing us at service@BrilliantDirectories.com.

**_How we protect your personal information_**

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. We use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information.

We want you to feel confident using our website to transact business. However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure. Please refer to the Federal Trade Commission's website at <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm> for information about how to protect yourself against identity theft.

**_Blogs, bulletin boards, reviews and chat rooms_**

We may provide areas on our websites where you can post information about yourself and others and communicate with others, as well as post reviews of products, establishments, contractors, and the like, or upload content (e.g. pictures, videos, audio files, etc.). Such postings are governed by our Terms & Conditions.  In addition, such postings may appear on other websites or when searches are executed on the subject of your posting. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. Once you have posted information, you may not be able to edit or delete such information.

**_Children's privacy_**

Our website is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

**_Visiting our websites from outside the United States_**

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy.

**_No Rights of Third Parties_**

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the website.

**_Changes to this Privacy Policy_**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. We recommend that you check our website from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.

**_How to contact us_**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, or if you would like to request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please contact us by e-mail as follows: service@BrilliantDirectories.com

Cookies:

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record keeping purposes. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time.

For example, when you sign in to our website, we will record your user or member ID and the name on your user or member account in the cookie file on your computer. We also may record your password in this cookie file, if you indicated that you would like your password saved for automatic sign-in. For security purposes, we will encrypt any usernames, passwords, and other user or member account-related data that we store in such cookies. In the case of sites and services that do not use a user or member ID, the cookie will contain a unique identifier. We may allow our authorized service providers to serve cookies from our website to allow them to assist us in various activities, such as doing analysis and research on the effectiveness of our site, content and advertising.

You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. (Click "Help" in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.) If you do so, some of the features and services of our website may not function properly.

We may allow third-parties, including advertising companies and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver, and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party's privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies ([www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)).

Web Beacons:

Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies which are stored on the user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in email) and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website.

### Give It a Whirl

_By Vincent H. – California, USA_

Hi my name is Vincent Hoss. I’m very happy with my Brilliant Directories website. I’ve been looking around for an easy-to-use website that Google is happy with for a number of years. I had quotes that were five times what I actually spent getting this site finished. This is my little helper here who helps me with the sites. Keeps an eye on things.

The thing is, it’s hard to find a site that’s easy to use, that’s easy to customize, and Brilliant Directories has been really easy to use. I ended up signing up for the onboarding to help me get the site together. Then I realized I wanted more custom things than they had on the onboarding so I ended up using the Marketplace. That’s worked out really good.

The site’s been up for about four weeks now and I get probably one to two calls per day but I do have 15 years experience in internet marketing and lead generation. So I must say that that the Brilliant Directories site was really the foundation that I needed to accomplish… I’ve tried so many different sites, so many different softwares that said they could do it but in reality it wasn’t easy to use, Google wasn’t happy with it, it wasn’t easy to customize, it bogged down and I stopped searching after this.

I’ve got several more sites under construction. If you’re thinking about doing a directory this seems like the perfect software to use. If you have questions or need any help you can reach me at VincentHoss.com. Again very happy with the software, the price was very reasonable, and I’ve been happy with it. And based on my experience I’m pretty sure you’ll be happy with it if you give it a whirl. Thanks.

via YouTube.com

×

### It’s Worked out Brilliantly

_By Dr. Kevin G. – California, USA_

Hello! I’m Dr. Kevin Grold. I’m the CEO of EDReferral.com and here you can see my homepage created with Brilliant Directories. It’s worked out brilliantly for me in that it’s allowed me to create many different ways for people to search for eating disorder treatment which is what we do.

So for instance on the homepage here when you open it up it automatically brings up all the icons of all the treatment centers and individuals and support groups in your local area automatically. Then we have a little video that explains all the different features of the site and if you scroll down you can visit our sponsors and you can also read about many different topics related to eating disorders.

But what I really like about the site is when you go to do a search Brilliant Directories allows me to create many different ways for people to search here that people can click on just to find treatment in their state, we can search by keyword here, we can also click on an icon map that was back on our homepage, or again click on a state in another way at the bottom. But what I really like is that there are specific ways for searching for treatment. And for instance if you clicked on let’s say “Eating Issues Treated” and then click on let’s say “Anorexia”… what it does is it automatically fills in your local area here and in Del Mar and you click search, what that does is bring up all the resources related to anorexia in my local area. And you can click on any of these highlighted treatment centers or individuals to read more about them.

What it’s doing is at the same time is creating a separate page for each one of these categories that you’ll see here. So for instance “Collaborates with” and then “College health centers” in Del Mar – that creates a separate page. That’s what I really like about Brilliant Directories. So for instance if I did a search on Google we’re going to see that I have over 40,000 pages – 40,000 different combinations that Brilliant Directories created for me so that I’ll have so many pages on Google and so many ways for people to find me.

And for instance if somebody types in “eating disorder treatment centers”, who’s going to come up first? EDReferral.com. So I’d like to say that Brilliant Directories is working out brilliantly for me and thank you for the amazing site.

via YouTube.com

×

### This Company Is Brilliant

_By Doris F. – Florida, USA_

Hi guys. My name is Doris Flewellen and I’m located in Pembroke Pines, Florida. I want to take the time to share with you my experiences with Brilliant Directories. First I’d like to say, yes, I highly recommend them. As a business owner and someone very new to the directory industry, I had no clue as to what it is I needed to do. I didn’t know where to start. I didn’t know where to begin. The customer service at Brilliant Directories is amazing. Ultimately, it’s the customer service and the warmth of the whole team that allowed me to make the decision as to whether or not I was going to purchase this software. And I’m glad that I did because the support, like I said, is amazing.

The company itself is brilliant. I have to tell you this story – I had so many membership levels in my directory it was ridiculous. And it was funny because I could just imagine the look on Jason’s [Brilliant Directories CEO] face when he was looking, like, “what is going on here?” And so what he did is he actually took the time to straighten that whole mess out for me at no cost to me. That was amazing.

I’ve not only bought one directory, I bought two. If you are skeptical/undecided as to whether or not this company is the company that you should purchase your directory from, take it from me, I highly recommend that you choose Brilliant Directories simply because the support from their customer service department is awesome. There’s not a time when I sent over a frustrating email and someone sent one back in frustration. It was always patience. They’re very patient with you because trust me, I have seen my fair share of angry emails out of my own personal frustrations of trying to figure out what it is I want to do, and when Jason [Brilliant Directories CEO] called me personally to say, “Hey, we don’t want you frustrated. We want to resolve the issue and we’re going to resolve it today…” I love that. I love that confidence in his voice knowing that he was not going to let me get off that phone upset like I was. And when I got off that phone I’ll tell you I was relaxed. It was a weight lifted off my shoulders and it was one less thing I had to worry about. And I thank them so much.

So again if you are undecided/not sure if Brilliant Directories is the route to take, I can tell you, you need to take it. No more hesitating. Do it today. You need to lock in on those promotions or whatever opportunity that was presented to you and jump on it because it’s definitely worth it.

Now my directory is generating money for me and I owe it all to Brilliant Directories. I owe it all to the team. Overall, to everyone who had a hand in putting this whole thing together, it’s amazing. I appreciate you guys. I love you guys! Thank you so much, guys. I highly recommend Brilliant Directories. Thank you!

via YouTube.com

×
